So even in the universe that some folks are still stuck in where electoral voting actually matters, I'm still right?
Democrats are finally admitting it. Harris lost support over Gaza.
And here's the thing. I was warning Biden and Harris for over a year personally in numerous direct conversations with each of them.
I kept saying that our refusal to hold the Israeli government accountable over the destruction and genocide in Gaza was morally, legally and politically wrong.
We kept being told it's not in the numbers. And it didn't just shape an election. It helped shape a crisis.
When leaders ignore the people, the consequences aren't just political, they're global.
Hey, guys. So before the day is done, I just want to point out that for Kamala to garner new voters, like voters that weren't already going to just vote for Biden, she would need to take a new direction.
Kamala, if your comms team is watching, which I know y'all be watching my page, I really hope, I really, really hope that you plan to do what needs to be done to cease and desist.
As the ICJ has said, all military practices in Gaza, East Jerusalem and the West Bank.
Mm-hmm. Immediately. I hope they're drafting the statement now. And I hope that you all are focusing on diversifying your donor base so that you are not solely married to the Zionist donor base that has continued this slaughter.